<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest News | DU Liang</title>
    <link>https://liang324.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://liang324.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Latest News</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2020-2021 liang324</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://liang324.github.io/images/icon_huafd8ec2e798752a6b5e4c81251c6512c_20750_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Latest News</title>
      <link>https://liang324.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next stage with SHU</title>
      <link>https://liang324.github.io/post/21-01-29-next-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liang324.github.io/post/21-01-29-next-stage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. DU Liang has got a job offer as lecturer from the Shanghai University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. DU Liang is expected to finish his contract with the R-GIRO program in Ritsumeikan University, Japan by this March. Now, he got a new job offer as lecturer from the Shanghai University, Shanghai, China. He will work with the Shanghai Key Laboratory of Intelligent Manufacturing and Robotics, School of Mechatronic Engineering and Automation after returning China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shanghai University (commonly referred to as SHU, or colloquially Shangda (Chinese: 上大; pinyin: Shàngdà)) is a public research university located in Shanghai. The 555-acre main Baoshan campus is situated in the north of Shanghai, and there are two other campuses in Jiading and Jing&amp;rsquo;an. Shanghai University is amongst the list of Project 211 for top national universities. &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shanghai_University&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;(cited from Wikipedia)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shanghai Key Laboratory of Intelligent Manufacturing and Robotics is one famous research team in robot field in China. Their research includes industrial automation, robots for health care, robots for farming, and basic robotic theories.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2021</title>
      <link>https://liang324.github.io/post/20-12-31-happy-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://liang324.github.io/post/20-12-31-happy-new-year/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Farewell 2020 and Happy New Year 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a difficulty year for almost everyone. The way we live and work has been completely changed. It is very likely that this new life-style, the post-covid era, will continue even when it all ends. However, this pandemic is also a valuable experience for everyone of us. It is only under such huge challenge that we discover the true meaning of life. We found that the most precious gift is our beloved ones. We found that we can develop new technologies to fight the great enemy of mankind. We found that if you try this new life, you may get new inspirations and new progresses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever, now we can say &lt;em&gt;Farewell 2020 and Happy New Year 2021&lt;/em&gt;. I hope all my friends will bring good luck to their lives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
